[
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "How does Bluetooth Classic handle privacy concerns compared to Bluetooth LE?",
        "options": [
            "Bluetooth Classic uses encryption keys for all data transmissions.",
            "Bluetooth Classic limits the number of devices that can connect simultaneously.",
            "Bluetooth Classic randomizes MAC addresses for improved privacy.",
            "Bluetooth Classic does not have any privacy features.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [3]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What is the Bluesnarfing attack?",
        "options": [
            "A vulnerability that allows unauthorized access to Bluetooth devices via malicious code execution.",
            "A method for securely pairing Bluetooth devices using encryption keys.",
            "A feature that enhances Bluetooth data transmission speed.",
            "A protocol used for secure pairing in Bluetooth devices.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [4]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Which security services does Bluetooth support?",
        "options": [
            "Authorization",
            "Confidentiality",
            "Authentication",
            "Notarization",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [0, 1, 2]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Which multiple access mechanism BT uses?",
        "options": [],
        "answer": []
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What is Bluetooth LE Privacy Feature?",
        "options": [
            "A feature that encrypts all data transmitted over Bluetooth Low Energy (LE).",
            "A feature that generates random MAC addresses for advertising packets.",
            "A feature that hides the Bluetooth device from unauthorized scanning.",
            "A feature that restricts the range of Bluetooth connections to improve privacy.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [1]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What is pairing in Bluetooth technology? Select one:",
        "options": [
            "A method for managing power consumption in Bluetooth devices.",
            "The process of establishing a Bluetooth connection between two devices.",
            "A mechanism for securely storing Bluetooth device information for future connections.",
            "None of the other options.",
            "A protocol for encrypting Bluetooth data transmissions."
        ],
        "answer": [1]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Consider the Bluetooth Authentication sketched in the figure below.",
        "options": [],
        "answer": []
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What is bonding in Bluetooth technology?",
        "options": [
            "A mechanism for optimizing Bluetooth connection range.",
            "A method for encrypting data packets during Bluetooth transmission.",
            "A process of permanently storing Bluetooth device information after successful pairing.",
            "A protocol for managing multiple simultaneous Bluetooth connections.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [2]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "What is the Relay Attack in Bluetooth?",
        "options": [
            "It bridges communications between devices to fool them into thinking they are close to each other",
            "It consists in brute forcing the PIN.",
            "It sends a previously recorded frame to misuse the communication.",
            "It leverages the signal to noise ratio to authenticate the device.",
            "None of the other options"
        ],
        "answer": [0]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "Which are the characteristics the Bluetooth devices must have to support passkey entry?",
        "options": [
            "Both devices must have a keypad and a display.",
            "Both devices must have a keypad, a display and a NFC reader.",
            "It is sufficient that both devices have a display.",
            "It is sufficient that one device has a keyboard.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [4]
    },
    {
        "type": "associate",
        "question": "Associate the correct definition to the correct Bluetooth Association Modes",
        "options": {
            "names": [
                "Passkey Entry",
                "Out-of-Band",
                "Numeric Comparison",
                "Just Works"
            ],
            "list": [
                "The user enters the passkey into the device which must have a keyboard.",
                "Use a mechanism that is not based on Bluetooth to associate.",
                "A number is displayed on the two devices and the user confirms the number is identical.",
                "Used for devices with no Display or Keyboard, with default passkey."
            ]
        },
        "answer": {
            "Passkey Entry": "The user enters the passkey into the device which must have a keyboard.",
            "Out-of-Band": "Use a mechanism that is not based on Bluetooth to associate.",
            "Numeric Comparison": "A number is displayed on the two devices and the user confirms the number is identical.",
            "Just Works": "Used for devices with no Display or Keyboard, with default passkey."
        }
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "How is a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack prevented in Bluetooth simple security pairing?",
        "options": [
            "By rotating the Bluetooth MAC address during the pairing process.",
            "By using public key cryptography for key exchange.",
            "By encrypting the pairing process using a shared secret key.",
            "By using a fixed PIN that is known only to the user and the device.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [2]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "In Bluetooth, the Security Level 3 - Authenticated Pairing with Encryption - guarantees which of the following properties?",
        "options": [
            "Man in The Middle (MITM) protection",
            "Device authenticate required",
            "Minimal user interaction - the user is not involved during pairing.",
            "No encryption keys are generated.",
            "None of the other options."
        ],
        "answer": [0, 1]
    }
]
